I have always counted with which you have
the anger of going in search of those dreams.
I cannot continue with your dreams
Now I go for mine.
You have a gift Peter. this great power...
he/she brings I get big responsibilities.
He/she takes my hand son.
No. uncle Ben.
Alone I am Peter Parker
I won't be but Spiderman
Never but
He/she hears
-Idiot
-I sit down it
-Thank you
-Of anything
Alone it follows the fire. hurry
When the border is similar to zero...
the volume is of...
Somebody please
1.3 elctrones volts
Good work today Parker.
it continues this way
I am not in fact the your you think
you should think that I am evil
If you are not it. you have been deceiving us
this whole time in a very bad way
I hope you are not
living a double life
Seeking to be evil and
to be good the whole time
Would that be hypocrisy?
Undoubtedly I have been inprudente
I am cheerful.
I am cheerful
You are not glad to hear it?
I am cheerful of hearing it
Of I toss. I love you that
I have been very bad to my form
You were wonderful.
it is a very good work
You didn't tell me that you came
He/she was afraid that said
that he/she didn't come
You are different
I clean my shoes.
I ironed my pants
I made my tasks
Now I make my tasks
Do you want to go out with me?
Peter. I marry
Let us always imagine that you
you married in the high of a hill
And who was the boyfriend?
You had not still decided it
You think that because you dressed my work
you can tell me with who I will marry
Once you told me that you loved me
Let that the things cooled down.
because I thought that he/she had to make something...
that I don't have to make
You arrive demaciado late
-Will you think it?
-To think what?
To give us an opportunity
Of what do you speak?
We will never achieve it
Non pudes to make it.
you don't allow yourself to take Peter
I don't believe that it is so simple
Undoubtedly not. because always
you complicate the things
You don't understand...
I am no longer an empty seat...
I am different
Hit me. and truth that I bleed
I have to leave
I will marry in a church
You are different
Lover agrees of
with that wedding. we won't go to the bankruptcy
Here they are...
To buy a Czar?
It gets something cheap.
some cocktail
Boss. I have a trash can that he/she says
that he/she has something that maybe want to see
You don't tell me that you have the
a martian head...
because if you make it you would be
the third this week
From where devils did you take out that?
Of the garbage
In the garbage?
It seems that he/she surrendered
He/she threw the towel
He/she abandoned their small and sad disfrás
Finally I have it.
the power of the press triumphs
If. if. if. look...
I believe that I deserve a
little of something for this reason
-I give you 50 dollars
-I can obtain but that that
I give you $100. young lady Brant gives him
to this man their money and give him a soap
Their wife this on-line one
-The flowers..
-Flores. As much as?
-You have to spend but
-You spend as if you put those...
Daisies in my tomb
Get them plastic
I have to leave.
I have a great report
NON MA SPIDERMAN
Spiderman. Spiderman...
Is there where you have gone Spiderman?
To where were you Spiderman?
We go man. give me the money
We go. give me the money
It aids
We go...
It is not fair that he/she has left this way...
It was a man pasífico
It was all that had
Aunt May...
-You don't have to punish yourself
-You that it didn't should
Alone it is that...
Your you wanted to take the underground and
the one wanted to take you
If it had stopped it...
The three were
taking together
I am the responsible one
Of what?
Of what passed the uncle Ben
But your you were in the library.
you were making your tasks
He took me to the library
but me never among
That you mean?
I went to another place
To another locus in quo I thought that
it would win some money
To buy a car...
What wanted was to impress Mary Jane
It happened so quick
I made the money and the type didn't pay me
And they stole it...
and the thief...
He/she ran toward my...
Detainee could have him but
what wanted was vengeance
and it allows it to leave
Allow it to escape
He wanted a car...
It tried to remove him that of uncle Ben...
The uncle Ben refused...
And then the it shot him
Uncle Ben was murdered that night
to be the only person
that he/she made the correct thing
Me....
I sustained their hand... when he/she died
I tried to tell it to you many times
Alone a propping-up but
THE POLICE SUSPICION DE SPIDERMAN
IN THE DEATH DE OSBORN
Where these?
I leave the whole night Mister
-This well
-He didn't like their father that...
they saw their work
Good night Burner
Hello Harry
Otto. what do you want?
The beautiful Tridium
I need but this you see
But Tridium these lunatic?
You will destroy the city
This crazy one
He/she hears. he/she hears
For. for
This well. this well
Descend. we will make a treatment
It kills Spiderman and I will give you
the whole Tridium that you need
He/she waits. bring it to me alive
How do I find it?
Peter Parker
-Parker?
He/she took him pictures to Spiderman
for the newspaper
He could tell you where it is
Get ready
Don't harm to Peter
CRIME 75% WHERE
THIS SPIDERMAN NOW?
Somebody. aids
Fire
I cannot find my daughter.
Have you seen it?
That somebody calls to those
firemen now
It aids
-Is somebody in that building?
-It seems that there is a boy in the second floor
To where do you go?
I already go
Everything is well. everything is well. they come. I will take out you of here. we go
We go
You were lucky boy
A fellow is caught in the 4to floor
It didn't achieve it
Well. we will lower the mangeras and to wind them. larguémonos of here
Listen. pick up the team. we leave
Is not it supposed that he/she has what wants?...
...what needs?
That it is supposed that he/she makes?
I should not enter without playing
Ahead
- Hello
Do you want a piece of cake of chocolate?
It is well
And a glass of milk?
I would love it
Well
Thank you
You have a message
- It belongs to your aunt
- Thank you
- That it happens?
- They gave me some more weeks but...
...I decided to send them to the hell. I will move
- I found a small apartment
- For that didn't tell me?
I am quite able of taking charge of the things me alone
...and Henry Jackson. the one of in front me this shaking hands and...
- ...I am giving him 5 dollars
- Is that Henry Jackson?
Yes
It is amusing what happens in two years
9 years of age and he/she has big aspirations
He/she listens. about my last visit...
The past is passed.
let us don't speak of that
Better we continue ahead or
let us bury him under the bridge...
...as you want but...
...but you had a great aptitude
in telling me the truth
And I am proud of tí
And I thank you and...
...I adore you Peter...
...so much. so much
Where are my chemistry books?
All those powdery things... I gave them
- I put the mascots there behind Sra Parker
- Thank you Henry
- Hello Peter
- Hello Henry. you are growing
Henry for that you don't put those kitchen books there?
It is well
Do you take pictures of Spider Man certain?
He/she used to make it
- Where he is?
- Henry and I agree...
...that we won't see more their picture in the newspapers
The...
- ...it gave up
- For that?
- He/she entered in problems
- Will certain return?
I don't know it
You will never know that he/she will make
- Spider Man
- For that?
He knows the problem
when you see it
Too many few they make it there outside
...flying for the surroundings in that way saving old men as me
He/she knows God him the same as Henry
a hero needs
One intrepid able to be sacrificed
for people
Giving the example to all us
Everybody loves the heroes
People adore them. she shouts them. her names scream
And years later will say as their
students are inculpated per hours
alone to see the one that sustained them
in their brasos...
for one second but
I believe that there is a hero in each one of us...
...that it maintains us honest...
...he/she gives us forces...
...he/she makes us noble...
...and finally he/she allows to die with pride
Even sometimes... we should be strong...
...and to give up that that more we want...
...although we don't agree
Spider Man made that for Henry and...
...the he/she wonders to where fué
He needs it
You also. you could rotate that desk...
...and to put it in the garage
- But don't feel strange
- It is well
To concentrate with force on what I want
I am of turn!... I am of turn!
My back
Oh my back
Affection. you are sure that not
do you want to invite your friend the photographer?...
...Peter Parker?
Positive
- I thought that he/she was your friend
- Peter Parker?
It is alone a great fool
The world is full with big silly
You are adorable
Alone it is the uniform
Would you recline your head back for me?
- To recline the head?
- Yes. make it
To recline my head back?
Better than in the moon
Do you continue here?
-Hello
-Surprised?
Mary
Thank you to come
Is all well?
He/she could say it
This is strange. not you neither as beginning
Your you know as the mind
it puts us traps
-Tell it to me to my
-Good...
The mind me juice a good one
A part of my olló what you told me
after the show that night
That different eras
But I didn't want to listen to you
He/she was afraid to trust you
But...
-I have been thinking in this respect
-He/she listens...
I have but to say
Me...
Maybe I have hurried the things
-I thought
-Does he/she wait a moment. What do you say?
I am saying...
That me...
I thought that it could be there
for you Mary Jane
But I am not able to
My mind is putting on traps
Do you love me or not?
Me...
No...
You don't love me
Kiss me
That he/she kisses you?
I need to know something
Alone a kiss
That it is happening?
Peter Parker
And the girlfriend
What do you want?
I want you to look for to your
friend Spiderman
Tell him that I wait for it in the tower
this at 3 in the afternoon
Not you where it is
Find it
Or I will take out him the blood of
their bones
If you put a single finger to her...
Will you make what?
It is not in any place of the world.
I sit down it. John
Everything is my blame.
I made that Spiderman left.
It is the only one that can stop Ocktavius.
Yes.
Spiderman was a hero.
I could not realize.
The era...
a thief. a criminal...
he/she stole me my trage
It is a threat for the whole city.
I want that that ball of hair
arácnida after the grills.
I want to hang it of their spider cloth.
I want Spiderman.
Where is she?
She goes to be well. Let us speak.
You have a train that to stop.
It aids. It aids.
I cannot stop the train.
- Spiderman.
- Oh god. everything ended up!
Tell to all that hold back well.
Do you have another brilliant idea?
I have some. Look.
Care!
He/she is stopping.
Put it in the floor... lowers it slowly.
Is it alive?
It is alone a boy.
It is not bigger than my son.
Everything is well.
We find something
I won't say it to anybody.
It is good to have you
again Spiderman.
He is mine.
If he/she wants it to him he/she has
that to fight first with me.
And with me.
With me also.
Very well.
Where do you want it?
And the Tridium?
Yes.
Before making you suffer
as you have made me you...
I want to see who there is
behind that mask...
and to look at you to the eyes.
Peter.
It cannot be.
Harry.
Where is she?
Where does he/she have it?
He has M.J.
-No. all that wanted was the Tridium
-The Tridium?
He/she is making the
machine again.
If it achieves it he/she will die half of New York.
Where is it?
Peter. you killed my father.
Things that are more are happening
big that our problems.
Harry please. I have to stop it.
He/she hears... he/she hears...
I am speaking with you.
You already have what you need
for your scientific proyectico...
now allow me to go.
I cannot allow you to go. you would bring to the police.
Anything will stop now
that Spiderman is dead.
It is not dead. I don't believe you.
Believe it.
Surprise.
As soon as...
I should imagine that him
it would never finish with you.
Turn off it Ock. you will make him
I damage a lot of people this time.
That is a risk that
I am willing to run.
But me nr.
Mary tolerates Jane.
Let us see like salts of this.
Now what?
Doctor Octavius.
We have to turn off this.
Please say I eat up.
Peter Parker.
Brilliant but idler.
Look at what is happening.
we have to destroy it.
I cannot destroy it.
I won't make it.
You were the one that me
he/she spoke that the intelligence...
it is a gift to use
for the humanity's good.
A privilege.
The fact of being different has him
transformed into something that is not.
Don't listen to them.
That was my dream.
Sometimes to make
the correct thing has to allow to go...
that that more we want.
even our dreams.
You are right.
He is right.
Listen to me.
Listen me now.
Now say I eat up to stop it.
It cannot stop.
Now you autosostiene now.
He/she thinks.
Unless...
the river...
allow it to fall.
I will make it.
- Hello.
This is really heavy.
M.J. in case we died.
You love me.
It is this way.
Although there are
said that or you would should.
I won't die being a monster.
I believe that I always knew who
you were really...
but I never said it.
Now you know for that
non podiemos to be together.
Spiderman will always have enemies.
I cannot let you to run that risk.
I will always be Spiderman.
Your and I will never be able to be together.
Hello.
Who walks there.
Son. I am here.
Dad?
I will tell you...
No. I am alive in you Harry.
now he/she plays you.
You swore to make Spiderman pay.
because you make it.
- He is my best friend.
- And me your father.
You are weak.
You were always weak.
You will always be weak until
that you take the control.
Now you know the truth Peter it has more than enough.
You strong. Harry.
Retaliate.
- Retaliate!
- No!
Tell them Débora.
That they will look for it.
Tell them that they don't open the Caviar.
I made that that taenia that to make
Mary Jane.
Surprised?
You should not be here.
You that you think
that it should not be here.
It is that you don't respect me enough
to allow me to take my own deciciones.?
I know that they will have risks...
but I want to face them with you.
It is but bad that alone we have the half
of our lives. half of us.
I love you.
So here I am stopped in your door.
I will always be stopped in your door.
Did at some time somebody save you the life?
I gave something.
Many thank you
Mary Jane Watson
You go after them Trigre
TC Attitude!
www.elantro.cl
 